Guide to the Yale Residential Colleges Student Printing Collection
Yale University Arts Library
Yale Residential Colleges Student Printing Collection
1936-2015
1936-2014
AOB 34
Yale University Arts Library
25
(31 boxes)
The collection contains a wide representation of the types of work created by student printers, primarily printed by letterpress. Posters, announcements, tickets, and other ephemera were usually created at the residential colleges to advertise events.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the student printers.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
The twelve residential colleges that make up Yale College have, in the past, each had their own printing facilities. The printing offices were started over a period of 30 years between 1937 and 1967, with Branford, Timothy Dwight, and Jonathan Edwards Colleges supporting the first wave of activity. The presses flourished in the hands of the students who used the facilities to produce advertising ephemera for campus activities and as a means to self-publish. Books were often created for specific Yale courses that taught the technique of letterpress printing. In the days before desktop publishing and the personal computer, letterpress printing was the method of choice for accessible and esthetically pleasing printed materials. As computer production became easier and better through out the 1980s, student interest in the presses waned. In the late 1990s a resurgence of interest in letterpress printing as a historic art form developed and the college presses became active again. The Lohmann Prizes were established in 1967 to honor Carl C. Lohmann 1910, founding member of the Whiffenpoofs and of the Honorable Company of College Printers and Secretary of Yale University from 1927 to 1953. The Lohmann prizes are awarded annually in May to distinguish excellence in undergraduate printing.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains a wide representation of the types of work created by student printers, primarily printed by letterpress. Posters, announcements, tickets, and other ephemera were usually created at the residential colleges to advertise events.
Arrangement
Organized in three series: Series I. Class and Course Projects; Series II. Lohmann Prize Projects; Series III. Residential College Books and Ephemera.
Series I is arranged alphabetically first by name of instructor, then by chronologically by year and alphabetically by student. Series II is arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically by student. Series III is divided into two subseries: Books and Ephemera. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically by the 12 residential colleges, then alphabetically by student.
- Class and Course Projects, Series I
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged by instructor, then by year of the class or course, then alphabetically by the last name of the student.
  - Class and Course Projects, by instructor
    - Altschul, Charles
      - [class project], 1990 (Box 12)
    - Baskin, Leonard
      - Howe, Con., 1972 (Box 1)
    - Strong, Tom
      - Daggett, Lucy, 1972 (Box 1)
      - Shakespear, George, 1972 (Box 1)
      - Thomas, Polly, 1972 (Box 1)
      - Warshauer, Dave, 1972 (Box 1)
      - unidentified, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Burton, Phillip
      - Mininberg, Julien [Lohmann Prize winner], 1985 (Box 12)
    - Frackenberg, David; Harder, Barbara; McCrillis, John; Noack, Gisela
      - Cash, George, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Gralla, Howard
      - Altschul, Charles, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Frackelton, David, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Fry, Beth A., 1978 (Box 1)
      - Rodman, Hillary, 1978 (Box 1)
      - Manning, Cecilia, 1979 (Box 1)
      - McCusker, Patrick, 1979 (Box 1)
      - McKee, Carol K., 1979 (Box 1)
      - Callison, Heidi D., 1981 (Box 1)
      - Penfield, Linda, 1981 (Box 1)
      - Seel, Anne, 1981 (Box 1)
      - James, Kathleen, 1982 (Box 1)
      - Joaquin, Nick, 1982 (Box 1)
      - Russell, J. Michael, 1982 (Box 12)
      - Thompson, Anders, 1982 (Box 1)
      - Weisenstein, Kristina E., 1982 (Box 1)
      - Li, Peter M., 1984 (Box 1)
      - Di Paolo, Philip J., 1984 (Box 1)
      - Scott, Kirk, 1984 (Box 1)
      - Kamensky, Jane, 1985 (Box 1)
      - Agulnick, Todd, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Howard, Esme, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Juhasz, Emeshe M., 1986 (Box 1)
      - Mackey, Ann, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Morgan, Rebecca L., 1986 (Box 1)
      - Roth, Alexander, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Weese, Catherine, 1986 (Box 1)
      - Murata, Yuki, 1993 (Box 1)
      - Robinson, Amanda, 1993 (Box 1)
      - Master, Allison, 2002 (Box 1)
      - Svoboda, Elizabeth, 2002 (Box 1)
    - McCrillis, John
      - Bellis, Tedric, 1972 (Box 1)
    - Murray, Jan
      - Weidenbaum, Marc; various, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Rose, Richard
      - Broadsides (includes Hunter, Stielau, Tsang, Wygant and Lohmann Prize winner), 2004 (Box 13)
      - Coleman, Amy [Lohmann Prize winner], 2004 (Box 1)
      - Gutfeld, Sonia von, 2004 (Box 1)
      - Hirschmann, Claire M. [Lohmann Prize winner], 2004 (Box 1)
      - Hunter, Rebecca, 2004 (Box 1)
      - Luna, Jose [2004 Lohmann Prize winner] (Box 1)
      - Porch, Emily [Lohmann Prize winner], 2004 (Box 1)
      - Silvia, Grace, 2004 (Box 1)
      - Stielau, A., 2004 (Box 2)
      - Tsang, Pansy, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Twersky, Sean, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Vladeck, Abigail, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Wygant, Lisa, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Zdanys, Kristina, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Class project – broadsides (including some Lohmann Prize winners), 2004 (Box 13)
      - Class project – postcards, 2004 (Box 2)
      - Anthes, Emily, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Bloom, Eric [Lohmann Prize winner], 2005 (Box 2)
      - Crisostomo, Chriselle, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Greenwold, Diana, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Huerta, James J., 2005 (Box 2)
      - Levy, Rebecca, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Lieu, Nita, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Lin, Shelly, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Ma, Iris, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Smith, Kirby, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Class project – Yalephabet (includes Lohmann Prize winners), 2005 (Box 12)
      - Class project – coasters, 2005 (Box 2)
      - Brown, Margaret, 2007 (Box 19)
      - Dowd, Bevan, 2007 (Box 19)
      - Gitlin, Basie [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Holdren, Sara [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 23)
      - Kurose, Emma [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Lu, Mindy, 2007 (Box 19)
      - McSpadden, James, 2007 (Box 19)
      - Nichols, Aurora [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 13)
      - Rae-Grant, Tucker [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Rosenblum, Lauren [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Seaver, Nicholas [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Shih, Iris [Lohmann Prize winner], 2007 (Box 19)
      - Smith, Rachel, 2007 (Box 13)
      - Zdanys, Joanna, 2007 (Box 19)
      - Class project - bookmarks, 2007 (Box 19)
      - Class project – broadsides (includes Lohmann Prize winners), 2007 (Box 19)
      - Class project – broadsides (includes Lohmann Prize winners), 2007 (Box 13)
      - Cronon, Hilary, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Divecha, Zai [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Gliwa, Catie [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Ho, Michelle [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Kenyon, Elsie, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Lemle, Julia [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Mich, Sarah, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Parnes, Ava Tattelman [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Penziner, Katherine, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Tung, Margaret, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Twarek, Bryan [Lohmann Prize winner], 2009 (Box 22)
      - Williams, Mathilde, 2009 (Box 22)
      - Dernbach, Matthew R., 2010 (Box 23)
      - Espinosa, Richard, 2010 (Box 23)
      - [K?, S?] "Things of Yale: A Pillow Book", 2010 (Box 23)
      - [Kim?, ?] "Literally Delicious Desserts", 2010 (Box 23)
      - Long, Matthew P., 2010 (Box 23)
      - Lydgate, Anthony [Lohmann Prize winner], 2010 (Box 23)
      - Marwanga, Loide, 2010 (Box 23)
      - [Otaye?,] Courtney, 2010 (Box 23)
      - Rose, Alix, 2010 (Box 23)
      - Wheeler, Olivia Hope, 2010 (Box 23)
      - Beck, Peter [Lohmann Prize winner], 2011 (Box 24)
      - Broussard-Wilson, Samantha [Lohmann Prize winner], 2011 (Box 24)
      - Leiby, Katie, 2011 (Box 24)
      - McCoy, Dakota E., 2011 (Box 24)
      - Neghaiwi, Brenna Hughes, 2011 (Box 24)
      - Perfecto, Rachel, 2011 (Box 24)
      - Taylor, Nate, 2011 (Box 24)
      - Tillemann-Dick, Glorianna, 2011 (Box 24)
      - "These Fragments", 2011 (Box 24)
      - Class project, 2011 (Box 24)
      - Indraligam, Renusha, 2012 (Box 25)
      - Katz, Spencer R., 2012 (Box 25)
      - Kim, Andrew, 2012 (Box 25)
      - Parnes, Greta [Lohmann Prize winner], 2012 (Box 25)
      - Oki, Kristi E., 2012 (Box 25)
      - Wang, Annie [Lohmann Prize winner], 2012 (Box 25)
      - Class project -- quotation cards, 2014; 11 (Box 27)
      - Boroski, C.A., 2014; 1 (Box 27)
      - Chen, Christine, 2014; 1 (Box 27)
      - Cho, Youn Jung [Lohmann Prize honorable mention], 2014; 1 (Box 27)
      - Farrell, Kendra, 2014; 1 (Box 27)
      - Jackson, Nubia, 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Lester, Grant, 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Rosenberg, Katherine [Lohmann Prize honorable mention], 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Thavychitch, Andrew, 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Zatarain, Henry J., 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Zhang, Olivia, 2014; 1 (Box 29)
      - Class project -- coasters, 2015; 9 (Box 31)
      - Class project -- broadsides, 2015; 9
      - Bianiz, Benjamin, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Harrington, Heather, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Houlihan, Seamus, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Huang, Tommy, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Ma, Julia, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Switzer, Sarah, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
      - Yan, Rebecca, 2015; 1 (Box 31)
  - Class and Course Projects, unidentified instructor
    - [for Art of the Book seminar]
      - Cochran, Kevin, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - [for Pierson College seminar: Creativity and Commerce]
      - Cacciato, Richard L., 1980 (Box 2)
    - [for senior projects / major requirements]
      - Ross, Michael, 1980 (Box 2)
      - Reichert, Amy K., 1981 (Box 2)
- Lohmann Prize Projects, Series II
  All entries are listed by last name of the student. As some pieces are collaborative, yet a single student won the prize, not every student who made the work is listed.
  - Lohmann Prize Projects, 1981-2004
    Scope and Contents
    From 1981 to 2004, variously both submissions and winners are included; winners are indicated if known.
    - Award certificate and announcement, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Goldstein, Bill [winner], 1985 (Box 16)
      See also Box 13.
    - Goldstein, Bill [winner], 1985 (Box 13)
      See also Box 16.
    - Kopp, Rochelle [winner], 1986 (Box 13)
    - Bator, Julia F., 1988 (Box 16)
    - Santora, L., 1988 (Box 16)
    - Brewster, Abraham [winner], 1991 (Box 13)
    - McGinty, Miko [winner], 1991 (Box 13)
    - Brewster, Abraham [winner], 1992 (Box 16)
    - Brewster, Abraham [winner], 1992 (Box 13)
    - Chen, Irwin [winner], 1992 (Box 16)
    - Chen, Irwin [winner], 1992 (Box 13)
    - Immerzilch, Quinsy [winner], 1992 (Box 13)
      Certificate only.
    - Laub, Peter, Syam Gadde and Ari Meyers, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Lee, Ahree [winner], 1992 (Box 16)
    - McGinty, Miko [winner], 1992 (Box 16)
    - McGinty, Miko [winner], 1992 (Box 13)
    - Phillips, Rich and Gabrielle Tenzer, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Rossbach, Christopher [winner], 1992 (Box 16)
    - Aoki, Carissa [winner], 1993 (Box 16)
    - Gadde, Syam [winner], 1993 (Box 13)
    - Felciano, Manoel, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Laub, Peter L. [winner], 1993 (Box 13)
    - McGinty, Miko, 1993 (Box 16)
    - McGinty, Miko, 1993 (Box 13)
    - Meyer, Ari B. [winner], 1993 (Box 13)
    - Sullivan, Andrew, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Bianconi, Claudia [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Bianconi, Claudia [winner], 1994 (Box 13)
    - Bruce, Ransom [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Chong, Jackson [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Liao, Marguerite [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Liao, Marguerite [winner], 1994 (Box 13)
    - Presto, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Robinson, Amanda, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Robinson, Amanda, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Streeter, George [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Streeter, George [winner], 1994 (Box 13)
    - Vaughn, Chelsea [winner], 1994 (Box 16)
    - Charles, Terrence [winner], 1995 (Box 16)
    - Corum, Jonathan [winner], 1995 (Box 16)
    - Goldberg, Jacqueline [winner], 1995 (Folder 1)
    - Hsueh, Aileen [winner], 1995 (Box 16)
    - Hsueh, Aileen [winner], 1995 (Box 13)
    - Liao, Marguerite [winner], 1995 (Box 16)
    - Hsueh, Aileen [winner], 1996 (Box 16)
    - Hovespian, Lisa [winner], 1996 (Box 16)
    - McCormick, Timothy [winner], 1996 (Box 16)
    - McCormick, Timothy [winner], 1996 (Box 13)
    - Scudamore, Alisa [winner], 1996 (Box 16)
    - Brown, Nathan and Shirley Liao, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Jayasekera, Mihira, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Landers, Heather [winner], 1997 (Box 16)
    - McCormick, Tim [winner], 1997 (Box 16)
    - Scudamore, Alisa [winner], 1997 (Box 16)
    - Amsterlaw, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Bemis, Alec; Gabriel Snyder, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Brown, Nathan; Justin Sacks; Katherine Spector, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Daniel, Eli, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Eleey, Peter [winner], 1998 (Box 16)
    - Hirway, Hrishikesh [winner], 1998 (Box 16)
    - Jayasekera, Mihira, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Krishnamurthy, Prem [winner], 1998 (Box 16)
    - McAlister, Sara, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Ochs, Juliana, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Su, Jennifer, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Taft, Genevieve [winner], 1998 (Box 16)
    - Woodruff, Rachel, 1998 (Box 16)
    - Daniel, Eli, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Hirway, Hrishikesh, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Jayasekera, Mihira, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Laszlo, Joelle, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Lin, Jimmy, 1999 (Box 16)
    - McAlister, Sara, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Ochs, Juliana, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Su, Jennifer, 1999 (Box 16)
    - McAlister, Sara, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Ochs, Juliana, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Thomas, Joaquin, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Edward-Corbett, Sara, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Giampietro, Rob, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Kuo, Leslie, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Lee, James, 2001 (Box 17)
    - Sud, Abhimanyu, 2002 (Box 17)
    - Dunn, Joshua [winner], 2003 (Box 17)
    - Gambell, Timothy, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Kuo, Leslie, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Kwok, Leslie [winner], 2003 (Box 17)
    - Lee, James, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Stielau, Allison, 2003 (Box 17)
    - Tsang, Pansy [winner], 2003 (Box 17)
    - Williams, Elizabeth (Betsy) [winner], 2003 (Box 17)
    - Futernick, Marisa, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Barthwell, David [winner], 2004 (Box 13)
    - Lee, James [winner], 2004 (Box 17)
    - Luna, Joseph [winner], 2004 (Box 17)
    - Tsang, Pansy [winner], 2004 (Box 17)
    - Kopley, Emily, 2004 (Box 17)
    - Hovland, Pamela, undated (Box 13)
    - Solomon, Ilene, undated (Folder 1)
    - Zelinsky, Paul, undated (Box 13)
  - Lohmann Prize Projects, 2005 to present
    Winners are organized by year and then alphabetically by the student's last name. Additional submissions—when available—are also grouped together by year, then alphabetically, and are housed with prize winners of the same year.
    From 2005 to the present, only the winners are listed.
    - Bloom, Eric [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2005.
    - Dalby, Owen [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
    - Kopley, Emily [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
    - Lee, James [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
    - Lee, James and Grave Silvia [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
    - Lee, James and Grave Silvia [winner], 2005 (Box 13)
    - Luna, Joseph [winner], 2005 (Box 18)
    - Holdren, Sara [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Kopley, Emily [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Lee, James [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Luna, Joseph [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Rae-Grant, Tucker [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Shih, Iris [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Shih, Iris [winner], 2006 (Box 13)
    - Tsang, Pansy [winner], 2006 (Box 18)
    - Gitlin, Basie [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2007.
    - Holdren, Sara [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Holdren, Sara [winner], 2007 (Box 23)
    - Kurose, Emma [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Nichols, Aurora [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Rae-Grant, Tucker [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Rosenblum, Lauren [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Seaver, Nicholas [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Shih, Iris [winner], 2007 (Box 18)
    - Rae-Grant, Robert Tucker [honorable mention], 2008 (Box 21)
    - Rudnick, David [first prize], 2008 (Box 21)
    - Smith, Rachel E. [honorable mention], 2008 (Box 21)
    - Sullivan, Margaret [first prize], 2008 (Box 21)
    - Divecha, Zai [honorable mention], 2009 (Box 22)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2009.
    - Gliwa, Catie [honorable mention], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Ho, Michelle [first award], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Lemle, Julia [first award], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Parnes, Ava Tattelman [honorable mention], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Twarek, Bryan [honorable mention], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Woo, Justin [honorable mention], 2009 (Box 22)
    - Espinosa, Richard [2010 honorable mention] (Box 26)
    - Lydgate, Anthony [2010 first prize] (Box 23)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2010.
    - Woo, Justin [2010 first prize (digital)] (Box 28)
    - Beck, Peter [2012 first prize (letterpress)], 2011 (Box 24)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2011.
    - Broussard-Wilson, Samantha [2012 honorable mention], 2011 (Box 24)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2012 honorable mention] (Box 26)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2012 honorable mention] (Box 28)
    - Lemle, Julia [2012 first prize (digital)] (Box 26)
    - Needle, Rachel [2012 honorable mention] (Box 26)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2013 first prize (digital)] (Box 27)
    - Lee, Jacqi [2013 honorable mention], 2012-2013; 2 (Box 31)
    - Parnes, Greta [2013 honorable mention], 2012 (Box 25)
      See also Series I: Rose, AOPW, 2012.
    - Sotirou, Andrew; Doyle, Paul; Huffington, Isabella [2013 honorable mention], 2012 (Box 27)
    - Wang, Annie [2013 first prize (letterpress)], 2012 (Box 25)
    - Fumerton-Liu, Lian [2014 first prize] (Box 31)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2014 honorable mention] (Box 28)
    - Lee, Jacqi [2014 second prize], 2013 (Box 31)
    - Ponce de Leon, Juan Pablo [2014 honorable mention] (Box 31)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2015 first prize - body of work], 2014-2015; 3 (Box 29)
    - Hwang, Cindy [2015 first prize - body of work], 2014-2015; 1 (Box 31)
    - Xu, Mariah [2015 second prize - body of work], 2014-2015; 7 (Box 29)
    - Xu, Mariah [2015 second prize - body of work], 2014-2015; 2 (Box 31)
    - Shatan-Pardo, David [2015 honorable mention], 2014-2015; 8 (Box 30)
    - Additional digital submissions, 2014-2015; 10 (Box 30)
    - Additional letterpress submissions, 2014-2015; 5 (Box 30)
    - Xu, Mariah [2016 first prize - body of work], 2015-2016; 3 (Box 32)
    - Preston, Oliver [2016 second prize], 2015-2016; 1 (Box 32)
    - Colford, Katie [2016 honorable mention], 2015-2016 (Box 33)
    - Colford, Katie [2016 honorable mention], 2015-2016
    - Siamof, Chloe [2016 honorable mention], 2015-2016 (Box 32)
    - Takahashi, Kai [2016 honorable mention], 2015-2016 (Box 32)
    - Additional digital submissions, 2015-2016; 12 (Box 32)
    - Additional letterpress submissions, 2015-2016; 2 (Box 32)
    - Van Lengen-Welty, Kiran [2017 first prize (digital)], 2016-2017 (Box 34)
    - Paolini, Christopher [2017 honorable mention (Digital)], 2016-2017 (Box 34)
    - Ma, Julia [2017 honorable mention (digital)], 2016-2017 (Box 34)
- Residential College Books and Ephemera, Series III
  This series is divided into two subseries: Books and Ephemera. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically by the 12 residential colleges, then alphabetically by author.
  - Books
    - Berkeley College
      - Diebold, William J., 1979 (Box 2)
      - Fitanides, Selena, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Kevles, Beth, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Branford College
      - Fellows of Branford College, 1943 (Box 2)
      - Hopkins, Adrian J.; Korobkin, Tess, 2006 (Box 2)
      - Landeryou, Mark, 1981 (Box 2)
      - Landeryou, Mark; Stebenne, David, 1981 (Box 2)
      - Oysterbed, 1940 (Box 2)
      - Oysterbed, 1941 (Box 2)
      - Wayzgoose, 1982 (Box 2)
    - Calhoun College
      - Ceputis, Eric A., 1981 (Box 2)
      - Corum, Jonathan, 1995 (Box 2)
    - Davenport College
      - Short, Randall, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Sullivan, Ann, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Ezra Stiles College
      - Aoki, Carissa, 1993 (Box 2)
    - Jonathan Edwards College
      - Ballantyne, Elizabeth, undated (Box 2)
      - Bolger, David P., 1979 (Box 2)
      - Chavez, Raul A., 1974 (Box 2)
      - Cho, Nancy, 1986 (Box 2)
      - Davis, G. B., 1970 (Box 2)
      - Ferguson, Lorraine, 1974 (Box 2)
      - Hidy, Lance, 1974; 3 (Box 2)
      - Hidy, Lance; Lydgate, William, 1967 (Box 2)
      - Hille, Jenny, 1969 (Box 2)
      - Johnson, Philip R., 1967 (Box 2)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. Directory, 1967 (Box 2)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. Jonathan Edwards College, 1978 (Box 2)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. A Recital of Song, 1937 (Box 2)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. Selected Poems of Edwin G. Burrows, 1938 (Box 3)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. Spider's Web, 1970; 2 (Box 3)
      - Jonathan Edwards College. Spider's Web, 1972 (Box 3)
      - Kandoian, Ellen; Hamilton, Jon [?], 1970 (Box 3)
      - Kols, Adrienne J., 1974; 2 (Box 3)
        General note
        See also Box 12.
      - Kols, Adrienne J., 1974 (Box 12)
        See also Box 3.
      - Libby, David, 1964 (Box 3)
      - Nelson, Douglas R., 1984 (Box 3)
      - Ritterbush, Stephen, 1970; 2 (Box 3)
      - Rodeas, 1970 (Box 3)
      - Sidell, Mark, 1974 (Box 3)
      - Stack, Nancy, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Tully, William, 1975; 2 (Box 3)
      - Wang, Meggy, 2002 (Box 3)
      - Zisman, J. M., 1978 (Box 3)
    - Pierson College
      - Altschul, Charles, undated (Box 12)
      - Boyle, Michael, 1978; 2 (Box 3)
      - Brotman, Alison B., 1978 (Box 3)
      - Browning, Barbara, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Cacciato, Richard L., 1978 (Box 12)
      - Celeste, Eric, 1982 (Box 3)
      - Celeste, Eric, 1983 (Box 3)
      - Cochran, Kevin, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Da Rif, Andrea, 1970 (Box 3)
      - D.S.R., H.L.K., M.J.B., M.S.R., 1977 (Box 3)
      - Forelle, Charles, 2002 (Box 3)
      - Garrett, David, 1988 (Box 3)
      - Goldstein, Linda, 1979 (Box 3)
      - Howarth, Anthony J.; Tashjian, Armen, 1953 (Box 3)
      - Howarth, Anthony J., et al., 1954 (Box 3)
      - Lane, John, 1978 (Box 3)
      - Mininberg, Julien [Lohmann Prize winner], 1984 (Box 3)
      - Nelson, Steven D., 1984 (Box 3)
      - Pierson College Press. The Australian, 1977 (Box 3)
      - Perrow, Margaret, 1981 (Box 3)
      - Reeder, Adam, 1986 (Box 3)
      - Rose, Gideon G., 1984 (Box 3)
      - Roth, Becca, 1984 (Box 4)
      - Sacco, David, 1982 (Box 12)
      - Salzberg, Steven, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Salzberg, Steven, 1979 (Box 4)
      - Segel, David, 1984 (Box 4)
      - Sonnenblick, Michael A., 1986 (Box 4)
      - Sweder, Betsy, 1982; 2 (Box 4)
      - Sweder, Betsy, 1983 (Box 4)
      - Thompson, Anders, 1983; 2 (Box 4)
      - Wang, Amy, 2002 (Box 4)
    - Saybrook College
      - Holmes, John R., undated (Box 4)
      - Reichert, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Silliman College
      - Angell, David, 1983 (Box 4)
      - Johnston, Robert W., 1982 (Box 4)
      - Olsen, Thomas G., undated (Box 4)
      - Schweizer, Gordon, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Timothy Dwight College
      - Andrews, John W., 1941 (Box 4)
      - Hulbert, Burton, undated (Box 4)
      - Timothy Dwight. Almanac for Academics, undated (Box 4)
      - Timothy Dwight. Almanac, Columbia: A Song, undated (Box 4)
      - Timothy Dwight. Almanac, Elegy Written in a Churchyard, 1938 (Box 4)
      - Timothy Dwight. Almanac, The Weathervane, 1945; 2 (Box 4)
      - Timothy Dwight. Almanac, The Weathervane, 1948 (Box 4)
    - Trumbull College
      - Bator, Julia, 1990 (Box 4)